Guide to the New York State Board of Mediation Cases 1952-1964
New York State Board of Mediation Cases
- AR 8502 - AR 8724 (1954). (Box 64)
  - AR-8723 New York Foods Corp., 1954 (Box 64, Folder 94)
  - AR-8724 Excel Pharmacal Co., 1954 (Box 64, Folder 95)
- AR 8725 - AR 8898 (1954). (Box 65)
  - AR-8726 Berke-Ressier Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - AR-8728 Ann Morris Confectioners, 1953-1954 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - AR-8729 Pennington Furniture, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - AR-8730 Cushman's Sons, Inc., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - AR-8732 Ferrara Confectionery Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - AR-8735 Inter-Lock-In Products Corp., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - AR-8736 Ford Instrument Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - AR-8739 765 East 166th Street, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - AR-8741 Radio Corporation, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - AR-8742 634 St. Nicholas Ave., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - AR-8743 Arlem Watch Case Corp., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - AR-8744 Hershey Furniture, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - AR-8746 Picture & Mirror Frame Mfrs. Ass'n, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - AR-8747 Robinson Plastics Corp., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - AR-8748 Standard Bldg. Prod. Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - AR-8749 Wee Moderns Inc., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - AR-8751-8753 Unique Optical Co, Mercury Opticians, Vogue Optical Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - AR-8758 Columbia Button & Nailhead Corp., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - AR-8759 Caravan Products Inc., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - AR-8760 Apex Brass & Bronze, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - AR-8761 American Zyloptic Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - AR-8762 H.B. Cohen Drug Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - AR-8763 Milllman's Restaurant, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - AR-8768 William Stern d/b/a Stern, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Borak Reporting Service New York No. 7, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Cushman's Sons, Inc, -and- Local 50, BCWU, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - AR-8770 1549 Townsend Avenue, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - AR-8772 1710 Montgomery Avenue, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - AR-8774 Charles Greenbaum, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - AR-8776 Continental Baking Co., 1954-1956 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - AR-8777 Bill & Eddie's Luncheonette, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Janssens Grayback Restaurant, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - AR-8782 Telco Television, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - AR-8784 Einhorn's Inc., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - AR-8785 Bond Bedding Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - AR-8787 Jay Kay Metal Corp., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - AR-8788 1727 Walton Avenue, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - AR-8789 1072 Woodycrest Avenue, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 38)
  - AR-8791 31-37 Nagle Avenue, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - AR-8792 Brunswick Decorators & Upholster., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 40)
  - AR-8794 John G. Purs. Mfg. Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - AR-8796 Mediation A.W. Rosen Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 42)
  - AR-8798 408 W. 150th Street, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 43)
  - AR-8800 Phil-Marr Upholstery Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 44)
  - AR-8801 Furniture Art Classics, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 45)
  - AR-8802 Brightman Leather Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 46)
  - AR-8805 Hillson Drug, Inc., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 47)
  - AR-8806 Holmes Private Ambulance, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 48)
  - AR-8807 National Biscuit Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 49)
  - AR-8808 La Salle Furniture, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 50)
  - AR-8809 Muskin Mfg. Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 51)
  - AR-8810 860 Fairmont Place, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 52)
  - AR-8811 Superior Machine Woodcarving Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 53)
  - AR-8815 Triboro Furniture Frame Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 54)
  - AR-8816 Savoy Upholsterers Shops, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 55)
  - AR-8618 Amplitel, Inc., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 56)
  - AR-8822 General Bronze, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 57)
  - AR-8825 New York Cameo Beauty Dept., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 58)
  - AR-8826 Canada Dry, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 59)
  - AR-8827 36 Ellwood Street, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 60)
  - AR-8828 2525 Grand Concourse 2537 Grand course, 1953 (Box 65, Folder 61)
  - AR-8330 Abbott Appliances, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 62)
  - AR-8831 Simon & Shapiro, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 63)
  - AR-8832 Ritz Interior Decorator, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 64)
  - AR-8833 Grodnick Textile Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 65)
  - AR-8849 Linden Drugs, Inc., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 66)
  - AR-8872 M. Ottenheimer's, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 67)
  - AR-8873 Daniel Jones, Inc., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 68)
  - AR-8874 1985 E. 15th Street, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 69)
  - AR-8875 Great Penny Store, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 70)
  - AR-8879 Sample Card Board of Trade, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 71)
  - AR-8880 Bee Line Inc. and Rockville Centre Bus Corp., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 72)
  - AR-8881 Central Plants, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 73)
  - AR-8884 Central Park Chemists Inc., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 74)
  - AR-8834 Busch Jewelry Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 75)
  - AR-8835 Morey Machinery Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 76)
  - AR-8838 270 Bronxville Road, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 77)
  - AR-8840 3764 Bronx Blvd., 1953-1954 (Box 65, Folder 78)
  - AR-8846 Manhattan News Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 79)
  - AR-8848 Berke Ressler Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 80)
  - AR-8891 Superior House & Window Cleaning, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 81)
  - AR-8893 232 West 1424 Street, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 82)
  - AR-8894 Best Ever Dairy Prod. Inc., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 83)
  - AR-8898 Wucker Furn Co., 1954 (Box 65, Folder 84)
- AR 8900 - AR 9199 (1954). (Box 66)
  - AR-8900 Century Projector Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - AR-8902 Samac Serv. Corp., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - AR-8903 Four Star Up. Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - AR-8907 Union News Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - AR-8912 Penguin Restaurant, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - AR-8913 Style Metal Specialties, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - AR-8914 Rose Art Finishing Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - AR-8915 Superior Arm, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - AR-8917 J.J. Hart, Inc., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - AR-8918 Heller Candy Corp., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - AR-8920 558 West 164th Street, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - AR-8921 568 West 173rd Street, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - AR-8927 Cutler - Hammer, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - AR-8929 Tru-Vue Optical, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - AAR-8930 Abbott Office & Window Cleaning Corp., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - AR-8931 Arrow Service, Inc., 1953-1954 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - AR-8938 East New York Fancy Basket Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - AR-8944 Majestic Chair Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - AR-8946 225 W. 59th Street, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - AR-8948 Parkview Tavern, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - AR-8949 391 E. 149th Street, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - AR-8950 911 Walton Avenue 923 Walton Avenue, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - AR-8951 2414 Creston Avenue, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - AR-8954 David Kopper Candy Corp., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - AR-8958 thru AR-8990 T. Sarno et al., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - AR-8968 M. Greenwald, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - AR-8969 P. Klatzman, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - AR-8970 R. Liff, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - AR-8987 George Spatafora, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - AR-8991 S&S Sheet Works, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - AR-8992 Allied Maintenance, 1953-1954 (Box 66, Folder 31)
  - AR-8993 Federal Bake Shops, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - AR-8995 400 Convent Ave., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 33)
  - AR-9000 Phoenix Brush Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 34)
  - AR-9003 Benjamin Kikoler, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 35)
  - AR-9005 Central Upholstery Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 36)
  - AR-9006 Recent Quality Furniture, Inc., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 37)
  - AR-9008 Box Spring Corp., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 38)
  - AR-9012 Hotel Bedding Co., 1953-1954 (Box 66, Folder 39)
  - AR-9016 16-18-20-24 Keough Lane, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 40)
  - AR-9017 1517 Walton Avenue, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 41)
  - AR-9019 237 North Broadway, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 42)
  - AR-9021 Larc Leather Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 43)
  - AR-9022 Atlas China Company, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 44)
  - AR-9023 ACME Concrete Burial Vault, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 45)
  - AR-9024 Bronx & Manhattan Retail Fish Dealers, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 46)
  - AR-9025 S&S Slip Cover Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 47)
  - AR-9026 Fireside Decorators, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 48)
  - AR-9029 Edward Gross, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 49)
  - AR-9031 Coca-Cola Bottling, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 50)
  - AR-9032 Pioneer Ice Cream Division (Borden Co.), 1954 (Box 66, Folder 51)
  - AR-9035 Jarnow & Company, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 52)
  - AR-9042 Steel Scaffolding Co. Inc., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 53)
  - AR-9044 Lincoln School of Radio & Television, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 54)
  - AR-9048 Metropolitan Sand & Gravel, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 55)
  - AR-9049 Tri-State Assoc. Tel. Corp., 1953-1954 (Box 66, Folder 56)
  - AR-9050 Steel Scaffolding Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 57)
  - AR-9053 Fisher-Stevens Service, Inc., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 58)
  - AR-9054 Reno Fab, Inc., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 59)
  - AR-9060 United Retail Fish Dealers Assn., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 60)
  - AR-9061 Anaconda Wire, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 61)
  - AR-9063 Cheesman Elliot Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 62)
  - AR-9065 60 West 129th Street, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 63)
  - AR-9066 Frederick Lopez, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 64)
  - AR-9073 Staffin Johns Company, 1953-1954 (Box 66, Folder 65)
  - AR-9074 Jack's Beauty Salon, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 66)
  - AR-9080 Inland Dry Storage Committee, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 67)
  - AR-9081 Marlin Mfg. Company, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 68)
  - AR-9083 American Pharmaceutical Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 69)
  - AR-9084 White Dental Mfg. Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 70)
  - AR-9090 Jolan Mfg. Company, Inc., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 71)
  - AR-9091 Sonotone Corporation, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 72)
  - AR-9093 Charles Greenbaum, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 73)
  - AR-9096 Metropolitan Jockey Club, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 74)
  - AR-9097 1113 Ward Avenue, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 75)
  - AR-9098 Ledo Industries, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 76)
  - AR-9104 Luckenbach Steamship Co., Inc. (Turner & Blanchard), 1954 (Box 66, Folder 77)
  - AR-9112 Frank Hauprich, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 78)
  - AR-9114 Nicholas Catalfamo, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 79)
  - AR-9115 Santa Di Fazio, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 80)
  - AR-9126 2705 Bainbridge Avenue, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 81)
  - AR-9127 3001 Henry Hudson Parkway, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 82)
  - AR-9132 Superior Die Cutting Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 83)
  - AR-9133 518 West 161st Street (Evha Realty Corp.), 1954 (Box 66, Folder 84)
  - AR-9135 Plastrix Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 85)
  - AR-9136 Okago Mfg., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 86)
  - AR-9140 Kern & Moss, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 87)
  - AR-9145 Star Upholstery Company, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 88)
  - AR-9148 General Bronze, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 89)
  - AR-9150 Paul Nielson, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 90)
  - AR-9152 New York Rubber Corporation, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 91)
  - AR-9154 552 West Broadway (Maysime Realty), 1954 (Box 66, Folder 92)
  - AR-9156 Keystone Company, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 93)
  - AR-9157 501-505 West 187th Street, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 94)
  - AR-9159 James Breslin, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 95)
  - AR-9160 Sperry Gyroscope Company, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 96)
  - AR-9162 Rex Baby Carriage Mfg. Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 97)
  - AR-9164 Eveready Plating Company, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 99)
  - AR-9165 Leschins Pharmacy, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 100)
  - AR-9167 Hunter Douglas Corporation, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 101)
  - AR-9168 Bedford Window Cleaning Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 102)
  - AR-9169 Bryant Window Cleaning Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 103)
  - AR-9171 Dry Dock Window Cleaning Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 104)
  - AR-9174 Pennsylvania House & Window Cleaning Co., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 105)
  - AR-9179 665 Burke Avenue (David Estates), 1954 (Box 66, Folder 106)
  - AR-9181 257 Valentine Avenue, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 107)
  - AR-9182 2350 Beaumont Avenue, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 108)
  - AR-9186 Gilton Mfg. Corp., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 109)
  - AR-9187 201 West End Avenue, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 110)
  - AR-9189 Standard Coated Products Corp., 1954 (Box 66, Folder 111)
  - AR-9190 NAPCO Corporation, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 112)
  - AR-9194 Reliable Slip Cover Company, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 113)
  - AR-9196 Canada Dry, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 114)
  - AR-9197 United Cigar Whelan, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 115)
- AR 9200 - AR 9456 (1954). (Box 67)
  - AR-9200 Imperial Cabinets Corporation, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - AR-9201 Sachs Upholstery Shop, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - AR-9202 I. Stein & Sons, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - AR-9203 Pico Food Truckers, Inc., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - AR-9206 Crown Tank Corporation, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - AR-9209 National Exhibition Co., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - AR-9213 Luckner Steel Equipment, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - AR-9214 Montauk Iron & Steel Corp., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - AR-9220 S.&E. Dinette Corporation, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - AR-9221 Peerless Sample Card, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - AR-9223 Hotel Ruxton, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - AR-9226 thru AE-9231 Atlantic Spring Products et Al., 1953 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - AR-9228 Automatic Bedding, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - AR-9230 York Feather & Down, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - AR-9232 Edro Photo Service, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - AR-9235 Novelty Belt Mfg. Company, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - AR-9238 980 Prospect Ave., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - AR-9240 Keystone Silver /Nc., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - AR-9241 Riteway Upholstery Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - AR-9243 Ocean Travel Bureau, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - AR-9246 King Baking Company, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - AR-9247 Video Woodcrafts Corporation, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - AR-9249 I. Axelrod, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - AR-9531 Building Maintenance Emp. Assn., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - AR-9252 Tri-Line Motors, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - AR-9257 515 East Lincoln Avenue (Lincoln Court Apts.), 1954 (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - John G. Purs Mfg. Co., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - AR-9260 Linden Parlor Frame Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - AR-9263 Eyton Mfg., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - AR-9264 Union News Company, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 30)
  - AR-9265 Allied Aviation Fueling of New York, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - AR-9266 Allied Aviation Fueling of New York, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 32)
  - AR-9270 Bilnor Corp., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - AR-9275 Coca - Cola Bottling, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 34)
  - AR-9276 Ashley Interior Decorators, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 35)
  - AR-9277 J. Chertok, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 36)
  - AR-9281 Wolfgang & Rosenthal, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 37)
  - AR-9283 thru AR-9293 Adams Refrigeration Service Et Al., 1955 (Box 67, Folder 38)
  - AR-9295 Roanwell Corporation, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 39)
  - AR-9297 Sunrise Mattress Co., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 40)
  - AR-9301 Allied Maintenance, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 41)
  - AR-9302 Allied Aviation Fueling of New York Inc., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 42)
  - AR-9303 M. N. Axinn Company, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 43)
  - AR-9306 Oregler Envelope Co., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 44)
  - AR-9310 501 West 189th Street et Al., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 45)
  - AR-9312 Crawford Clothes, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - AR-9317 thru AR-9326 Joseph H. Benzing Lumber Co. et. Al., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 47)
  - AR-9334 Ford Instrument, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 48)
  - AR-9337 Ike Cash, Jr., 1957 (Box 67, Folder 49)
  - AR-9338 232 West 142nd Street, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 50)
  - AR-9342 Jewish Theological Seminary, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 51)
  - AR-9340 Music Hall Restaurants, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 52)
  - AR-9344 Newport Optical, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 53)
  - AR-9348 Di Terese Bakery, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 54)
  - AR-9350 3555 Netherlands Avenue, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 55)
  - AR-9352 984 Bronx Park So., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 56)
  - AR-9354 Ledkoted Products, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 57)
  - AR-9355 Heller Bros., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 58)
  - AR-9356 Foremost Super Food Market, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 59)
  - AR-9357 Allied Maintenance Corp., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 60)
  - AR-9358 Dixie Furniture Inc., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 61)
  - AR-9359 Hyde Park Iron Works, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 62)
  - AR-9361 thru AR-9364 De Lellis Carting Co. et Al., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 63)
  - AR-9363 B. Cosenza, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 64)
  - AR-9365 James Nola, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 65)
  - AR-9368 John Constantino Upholstery Shop, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 66)
  - AR-9369 Terminal Barber Shops, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 67)
  - AR-9370 Coca-Cola Bottling, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 68)
  - AR-9371 Emerson Radio & Phonograph, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 69)
  - AR-9373 Sperry Gyroscope, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 70)
  - AR-9376 Manne & Son, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 71)
  - AR-9377 Conver Steel & Wire Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 72)
  - AR-9380 1869 Walton Avenue, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 73)
  - AR-9382 Fliegel's Hosiery, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 74)
  - AR-9383 Mutual Motor Sales Corporation, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 75)
  - AR-9385 Gerben Contracting Co., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 76)
  - AR-9386 Zylo Ware Corporation, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 77)
  - AR-9387 Louis Friedlander, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 78)
  - AR-391 Steel Scaffolding Co., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 79)
  - AR-9393 Plastic Sealers Company, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 80)
  - AR-9394 Padded Accessories Corp., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 81)
  - AR-9400 Simon Zucker Company, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 82)
  - AR-9401 1082-1084 Gerard Avenue, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 83)
  - AR-9404 92 Hamilton Avenue, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 84)
  - AR-9405 1710 Montgomery Avenue, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 85)
  - AR-9406 U.S. Studio & Mattress, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 86)
  - AR-9410 Brooks Quality Furniture, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 87)
  - AR-9414 Abbott Office + Window Cleaning, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 88)
  - AR-9415 Kay Mfg. Corp., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 89)
  - AR-9417 Ever-Ready Porter Service, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 90)
  - AR-9418 Oxford Boyswear, Inc., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 91)
  - AR-9421 R.K. Baking Corp., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 92)
  - AR-9428 Standard Keil, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 93)
  - AR-9433 Jamaica Brass Mfg., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 94)
  - AR-9437 Fred's Haircutting, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 95)
  - AR-9438 Reliable Machine Works, Inc., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 96)
  - AR-9440 3804-06 Bailey Avenue, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 97)
  - AR-9315 Red Devil Restaurant, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 98)
  - AR-9441 1727-9 Walton Avenue, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 99)
  - AR-9446 Jewish Technology Seminary, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 100)
  - AR-9448 Witty Bros., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 101)
  - AR-9455 thru AR-9464 Adler's Bed Spring Company et Al., 1954 (Box 67, Folder 102)
  - AR-9456 Bilt Mor Box Spring Company, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 103)
- AR 9459 - AR 9749 (1954). (Box 68)
  - AR-9459 Sleepmaker Bedding Corporation, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - AR-9460 Sleepwell Metal Bed Company, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - AR-9461 Standard Mattress Company, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - AR-9462 Sunnyside Mattress & Bedding Co., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - AR-9464 Zimet's Bed Spring Corp., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - AR-9467 1675 Grand Concourse, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - AR-9470 Sidney Sugerman, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - AR-9473 Wagner Baking, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - AR-9474 Ideal Optics, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - AR-9476 Rockwood & Co., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - AR-9477 Morey Machinery, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - AR-9478 ford Instrument, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - R-9485 Keystone Express, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - AR-9487 2425 to 2465 Haring Street, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - AR-9492 Gordon Baking Company, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - AR-9493 World Metal Spinning Core, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - AR-9494 Renart Sportswear, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - AR-9499 City Tank Corp., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - AR-9511 Park Surgical Company, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - AR-9514 576-600 Timpson Place, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - AR-9516 28 Caryl Avenue, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - AR-9523 Reflecto Letters, Inc. and Crown Lens Company, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - AR-9526 thru AR-9528 A. Basso Trucking Company et Al., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - AR-9530 Pepsi-Cola, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - AR-9531 General Bronze, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - AR-9532 Progressive Restaurant Owners, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - AR-9537 Furniture Art Classics, 1953 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - AR-9538 6241 Broadway, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - AR-9543 Center Optical Company, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - AR-9545 Central Upholstery Co., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - AR-9547 Mt. Vernon Knitting Mills, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 31)
  - AR-9548 Acme Metal Spinning Company, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 32)
  - AR-9546 Ritz Interior Decorators, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 33)
  - AR-9554 Perfect Handkerchief Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 34)
  - AR-9556 I.D. Watch Case, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 35)
  - AR-9563 Dukraft Mfg. Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 36)
  - AR-9565 J.F.D. Mfg. Company, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 37)
  - AR-9566 Lewis Steel Prod., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 38)
  - AR-9569 Steuben Mills, 1953 (Box 68, Folder 39)
  - AR-9570 Well Done Upholstery Co., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 40)
  - AR-9571 Electronic Instrument Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 41)
  - AR-9574 Colombo Restaurant, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 42)
  - AR-9575 Metropolitan Engraving Corp., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 43)
  - AR-9576 55 Sheridan Avenue, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 44)
  - AR-9578 1512 Drug Store, Inc., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 45)
  - AR-9580 Krug Baking Company, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 46)
  - AR-9584 Federal Bake Shops, Inc., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 47)
  - AR-9586 Fink Baking Corporation, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 48)
  - AR-9593 Tyler Made Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 49)
  - AR-9595 Jewish Child Care Assn., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 50)
  - AR-9596 National Motor Rebuilding Corp., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 51)
  - AR-9597 Patterson Bros., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 52)
  - AR-9600 Novelty Belts Mfg., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 53)
  - AR-9601 Inwood Motors, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 54)
  - AR-9604 Parodi Cigar, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 55)
  - AR-9605 Pearl Curtains, Inc., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 56)
  - AR-9608 Kings Hudson Sales & Service Inc.-and- Hollywood Hudson Sales & Service, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 57)
  - AR-9609 Ford Instrument Company, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 58)
  - AR-9614 Metropolitan New York & New Jersey Casket Mfrs. Assoc., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 59)
  - AR-9616 735 Mace Avenue, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 60)
  - AR-9620 L. & S. Grocery Inc., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 61)
  - AR-9621 Michael Dipenta, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 62)
  - AR-9623 2 West 1201th Street, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 63)
  - AR-9624 General Baking Company, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 64)
  - AR-9626 Pildes Co., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 65)
  - AR-9628 X-ray Mfg., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 66)
  - AR-9631 Artcraft Upholstery, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 67)
  - AR-9632 Stagg Tool & Die Company, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 68)
  - AR-9637 Cabble Wire Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 69)
  - AR-9639 Progressive Bronze Company, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 70)
  - AR-9642 Starrett Television Corporation, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 71)
  - AR-9643 Classic House, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 72)
  - AR-9644 Ford Instrument, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 73)
  - AR-9645 B & F Furniture, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 74)
  - AR-9648 14 University Place - Portchester, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 75)
  - AR-9652 Interboro Furn. Mfg. Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 76)
  - AR-9654 James Ippolito, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 77)
  - AR-9659 M.E. Stern, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 78)
  - AR-9660 M.H. Harris, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 79)
  - AR-9662 Permadente Co., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 80)
  - AR-9663 Local 891, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 81)
  - AR-9664 Star Novelty, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 82)
  - AR-9668 P. Sievering, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 83)
  - AR-9671 Little Fashion Togs, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 84)
  - AR-9672 - AR-9674 Mike's Carting Et Al., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 85)
  - AR-9675 Falcone Bakery, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 86)
  - AR-9684 Rays Appliance Center, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 87)